# LE YANG

### Personal Information

Address: 12150 Ams Run, Carmel, Indiana, 46032

PHONE: (718) 751-5228 EMAIL: le.yang@gmail.com

#### Professional Summary

More than 13 years working with various information platforms, and 10 years working with the Allscripts Sunrise platform, including Clinical Manager, Emergency Care, eLink, SIM, and CDS; Core, interface, and customization team lead with major configuration and development experience; Implementation architect for workflow analysis and design, implementation, build, training, and activation support; Ability to create a safe and efficient patient care environment with process improvement and technology; Experience with business intelligence platforms and data analysis

#### CORE COMPETENCY

- Project management
- · Process review and improvement
- Requirements gathering
- · Critical thinker
- · Knowledge engineering
- Team leadership
- Compliance program development

- Customer support and issue resolution
- Training development
- · Clinical system implementation
- Communication and interpersonal skills
- · Perform well under pressure
- · Attention to detail
- Proven track record of project delivery results

#### Professional Experience

2021-04-01-2023-01-01 | Custom Content Developer University Hospitals, Ohio

- Develop Medical Logic Modules (MLM) using Arden Syntax standards to supplement system logic including alerts and hard stops, data integration, result processing, order generation, enforcement of adherence to workflows and automation of document or order entry.
- Plan, manage and lead the development, implementation, ongoing maintenance, testing, and support of the MLM enhancements to the enterprise clinical system.
- Monitor the system on a daily basis to ensure data integrity, consistency and accuracy.
- Work with other application team members to determine strategies for meeting service-specific needs through the implementation of MLM.
- Integrate standard-based technologies within the Allscripts platform to deliver platform agnostic solutions to work orders and service requests.

2016-03-01-2021-06-01 | MLM Writer University of Kentucky Healthcare, Kentucky

- Develop Medical Logic Modules (MLM) using Arden Syntax standards to supplement system logic including alerts and hard stops, data integration, result processing, order generation, enforcement of adherence to workflows and automation of document or order entry.
- Plan, manage and lead the development, implementation, ongoing maintenance, testing, and support of the MLM enhancements to the enterprise clinical system.

- Monitor the system on a daily basis to ensure data integrity, consistency and accuracy.
- Work with other application team members to determine strategies for meeting service-specific needs through the implementation of MLM.
- Integrate standard-based technologies within the Allscripts platform to deliver platform agnostic solutions to work orders and service requests.

2017-07-01-2018-11-01 | Intergration Consultant | Jefferson Regional Medical Center, Arkansas

- HL7 Interface Engineer with Allscripts integration engine, eLink.
- Facilitated the planning of and execution of various integration initiatives to meet enterprise technical, security, and business requirements.
- Optimized integration and data flow strategy. Provided research data support to leadership in decision making process.
- Developed bi-directional interfaces to support data exchange between enterprise registration system (Soarian Financials), clinical system (Sunrise Clinical Manager), and various ancillary systems to support both standard messaging events and custom processes.
- Introduced documentation management system to client. Authored and maintained extensive technical documentation related to interface development and business processes.

2010-10-2016-03 | Implementation Consultant St. Vincent Health, Indiana

- Developed custom tools and tabs leveraging Allscripts ObjectPlus platform. Executed full software development cycle from requirements gathering to testing to preparation of turn-over documentation including functionality overview, workflow diagrams, and technical references.
- Developed complex MLM for clinical decision support, including many automated processes. Drafted architectural design guidelines for MLM development to improve coherence among direct and indirect execution of multiple MLMs to aid with process efficiency and to reduce failure points.
- Integrated ObjectPlus technologies with MLM development to deliver best user experience and process outcomes.
- Developed custom scripts to automate repetitive tasks: standard policy maintenance, charge maintenance, design point documents (formatting), test scripts (formatting).
- Developed custom queries for custom and ad hoc reporting, quality assurance, and feasibility analysis.
- Optimized stored procedures to improve query efficiency and accuracy.
- Lead projects to implement Sunrise platform to network hospitals to enable majority system function (CPOE, Pharmacy, Emergency Care, etc.) and to meet Meaningful Use requirements. Conducted future state analysis and addressed workflow gaps.
- Lead system upgrade projects. Performed impact analysis and lead design sessions, assisting end users with decisions on new functionality.
- Managed and supported system integration for Nutrition Services. Developed workflow recommendation and maintained related configuration items.
- Supported activation of various projects including big-bang CPOE rollout and system upgrades.
- Documented and categorized model system workflows, processes, and configured options.
- Conducted shared learning and knowledge sharing for team members.

#### TECHNICAL COMPETENCY

- Sunrise Clinical Manager (SCM)
- SCM 17.3 Training completed
- HL7 interface design and development (eLink)
- Business intelligence

- Testing planning and execution
- Custom program development
- External data exchange
- Medical Logic Module (MLM) authoring

- Scripting and task automation
- Data processing and transformation

• Structured content and presentation

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Expert: Arden, HL7, T-SQL

Intermediate: LaTeX, C#, XML/XSLT, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, web service (RESTful), re-

StructuredText, Python, WPF, VBA, HTML, Splunk, SSIS/SSRS, PowerShell

Basic: Shell Script, awk, sed

## EDUCATION

June 2009 Baruch College, City University of New York, New York City

Master of Science in Finance

May 2007 Queens College, City University of New York, New York City

Bachelor of Arts in Computer Science

Minor in MATHEMATICS

#### CERTIFICATION

MARCH 2018 Microsoft Certified Solutions Expert (MCSE): Data Management and Analytics

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA): SQL 2016 Database Development